

CONTACT

www.pablonudel.com

pablonudel@gmail.com

Toulouse, France

in pablonudel

pablonudel

LANGUAGES

Spanish French English

SOFTWARE

Visual Studio Code Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Adobe AfterEffects Adobe XD Blender

SKILS

Html 5
Css 3 & Sass
Tailwind
Bootstrap
Javascript
ReactJS
ThreeJS
NextJS
NodeJS
ExpressJS
MongoDB
SQL

Git

PABLO NUDEL

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

As a freelance, I worked in various creative disciplines, including Art Direction, Illustration, Motion Graphics, 2D Animation, Graphic Design and Web Design. Currently, I have focused on front-end development as I continue to expand my knowledge in this field.

EXPERIENCE

03/2022 - 06/2023 Web Builder & Design Project Associate

@ Luxury Presence

As a web builder, I created websites for luxury real estate agents and brokerages. This included implementing, configuring, and optimizing custom assets and components.

As a Design Project Associate, I performed QA, CSS improvements, tracking, feedback, and approvals in the stages leading up to site launch.

2007 - 03/2022 Freelance Art Direction, Illustration, Motion Graphics

& Graphic Design

Over several years, I managed and developed comprehensive projects for personal clients to which I've contributed my expertise in various design and visual arts domains. Additionally, I've integrated as a consultant to diverse teams within numerous audiovisual production studios, including: Turner International Argentina, Gazz, StoryStudio, Mandinga, Candela Creative Group and Gato.

Clients: MTV, Coca-Cola, TCM Channel, Citi Bank, Personal.

09/2004 - 04/2007 Project Manager of Multimedia Department

@ IMC Comunicación

I carried out various multimedia projects, landing pages, and product presentations. I collaborated in project management and team coordination.

Clients: Microsoft, Nokia, Pirelli, PwC.

06/2002 - 03/2004 Graphic Design

@ GR Group

Branding, Corporate identity, Editorial Design, Multimedia Design.

ACADEMIC EDUCATION

2001 - 2007 Graphic Design

@ Universidad de Buenos Aires Not finished (90% complete)

COURSES & CERTIFICATIONS

09/2021 - 11/2022 Full Stack Development

@ Coderhouse

HTML, CSS, Git, GitHub, Boostrap, Sass, SEO, Javascript, React, Node.Js, Express, API RESTFul, Websockets, MongoDB, SQL, Testing, GraphQL